You bastard.
It was you guys, right?
Who burned down my bar!
Hey.
Singha.
Hurry up.
Hey.
There's no blood.
Not even a scratch.
You're invulnerable.
What the fuck is that?
Who are you and where are you from?
There are bloody talismans
all over the side of the boat.
They were painted by hand with actual blood.
It's some kind of occult
calligraphy or sacred geometry.
It seems the victim.
Ate some rotten food.
With no idea it was all rotten stuff.
Then it built up inside the body.
The body was
severely inflamed for a long time.
Until they eventually died.
Hey.
Maybe they didn't know
they were eating rotten stuff?
Like fermented fish or sour pork?
No.
You know what they actually ate?
Lizards.
Geckos.
Centipedes.
Those aren't things people
typically preserve for food.
Take the mask off.
It smells just as bad either way.
Here.
Use this balm instead.
Rub it in.
And...
Every corpse ate this? Isn't that weird?
Right it's weird.
But what's weirder is
when they were eating this shit,
they saw it as something else.
That's why they ate it.
And they ate a lot of it too.
My dad used to say, when people use black magic.
On each other.
They cast a spell to make people see that filth
as real food.
It becomes toxic inside them. When they die,
there's no evidence left to catch the killer.
They ate it themselves.
Doc.
What about this cut on the forehead?
Is it related to the case?
(I'll be right back,
I need to sort things out with Blue.)
Who are you?
- Hey.
- Hey, Hey, Hey.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm here to help.
Hey, you.
Hey!
Hey, you. Hey! Stop it.
Hey.
Water.
Thirsty.
Oh, hey.
You.
You. You.
Why didn't you answer the phone?
But I already told the Boss.
That Singh and I are done with the drug running.
He's fine with it.
But I'm not!
I said you don't quit, so you stay put!
No quitting.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
You my father?
Shit.
You fucking punched me?
You fucking punched me? Huh?
You little piece of shit!
Know your place, bastard!
- Blue, what the hell are you doing? Let me go!
- Hey!
Hey, let go! Get the fuck off me!
Tell your men to let me go.
Hey.
Hey, let me go!
Fuck! Let me go! Fuck!
Let me go!
Did I kill your fucking parents or something.
Don't let me get loose, you fucker! Let me go!
Shit!
What the hell did you just do?
I'm not afraid of you!
Blue.
Please, I'm asking you.
He's my friend.
Singha.
If you want him.
Then work for me.
I won't do it.
Let my friend go!
If you're so tough, come and get him then.
Hey.
Stay the fuck away from us!
Do you hear me?
I heard you! Get it off!
Are you okay?
Shit.
Drop this case.
I'll take over from here.
This case is strange.
There are links to the Dan Chang incident.
It’s weird.
Several officers on the scene claimed.
The shooter couldn't be
Shot that he had protection.
This is insanity.
And now this case.
The report says the suspect is bulletproof again.
Who would believe a report written like this?
The Deputy said to switch the lead on this case.
But you know.
I wrote what I saw in that report.
Hem's gang.
Everyone knows they are bulletproof
and blade - proof.
They use black magic.
Who'd believe it?
How many people in the department.
Would believe.
It's different out here.
Drop the case for now.
I’ll handle it.
Would you like some fried shrimp or crab?
fried shrimp or crab?
No. I need sleep.
- Want some?
- I haven't slept at all.
You wanna die? Get lost!
Go!
What can I get you?
You.
Here.
The menu.
Kid.
Huh?
Kid... are you from around here?
Yeah.
Hey, what's with you?
Why are you touching me?
- What can I get you?
- Can I ask you something.
Living with your mom?
Sigh, shit.
You don't have a husband yet, do you?
Hey, old man. If you're not ordering,
then get out.
Are you gonna order or not?
I'm ordering.
I'll order. I'm hungry.
- I need food. A lot of it. I'm hungry.
- Yeah. What do you want?
You're beautiful.
So beautiful.
Are you gonna order or not?
Foon.
Auntie.
Go check the front of the shop for me.
Hurry up!
Shit, is it that bad?
เWait. I need to help close the shop first.
Damn it.
That customer was strange.
Didn't seem Thai at all.
Strange how?
Something happened?
No. it's fine.
He left.
I'll help Mom close up,
then I'll catch up with you guys.
You want anything?
Nah.
I'm good.
Alright, that's it then.
I heard her ask if you guys wanted anything.
Don't you think you should've asked me too?
You want to call her back and hear her nag?
Should you see a doctor?
Doctor?
After you bandaged me like this?
What were you thinking?
Antiseptic and a pack of Tylenol?
I got stabbed, you idiot, not fell into a thorn bush!
Well, I'm not a doctor. I...
I did what I could.
I'm not going anywhere.
This is fine. Just a scratch.
Far from my heart.
But what about you?
You gonna see a doctor?
What doctor?
Oh.
There.
Hey, let me tell you this.
Your charms.
Aren't for show.
If people see them,
they're going to want them.
They'll steal them from you
before you even realize it.
Be careful.
No.
Don't.
What was that noise?
No.
How do I know?
Stop.
Fuck.
Don't.
- Watch your hand.
- The other one.
No.
This one keeps moaning.
Stop.
Don't
No.
Don't.
I'm hurting more and
I’m not even making a sound.
Look at her.
Hey.
She's the one who need a doctor.
No.
Don't.
Right this way, Inspector.
You two, go and search the entire building.
Check for any witnesses.
- Go.
- Yes, sir.
Based on the condition of the bodies.
It looks like they shot each other.
Oddly, all the bodies.
Have Khmer script carved on their foreheads.
I spoke with the morning cleaner.
He’s Khmer.
According to him, those markings.
Are actually people's names.
The first responders didn't see
who made these marks.
I'm not sure either, sir.
This way.
Lieutenant.
Go and conduct further interviews with the staff.
Yes, sir.
Captain.
where is the security room?
This way, please. Follow me.
You can speak Thai, right?
Yes, I can.
Let me ask again.
What does that script actually mean?
They are names.
Each body has a different name.
So...
why write them?
And why a different name for each one?
It's written to claim the body for that name.
Making the original soul unable
to recognize its own vessel.
The shaman uses his bound spirits.
To take over and judge these sacrificed bodies.
Yes, Inspector.
What room is this?
It’s the staff storage room, sir.
How many workers were here this morning?
Only one, as far as I know.
Can we go in?
Yes, sir.
Inspector!
Lieutenant, get back! That's the killer!
Hey.
Stop right there, or I'll shoot!
Shit.
Hey.
What the fuck?
All units.
Suspect is wearing a white shirt
and a cream - colored hat.
He's fleeing through the hotel's back exit!
Intercept and detain him now!
Singha.
You can run from anything.
But you can't escape your own karma.
Just like your father.
Just like yourself.
To stand above all others.
You must trade your soul for the Occult.
And how about you?
I'm just a practitioner of the dark arts.
But you were born under the Saturday the Fifth star.
When Shiva ground ten king tigers into powder.
Then wrapped them in purple silk.
Sprinkled them with divine nectar.
And birthed a god.
We all have our elements.
Yours is Wind. Your father's was Earth.
What's that got to do with me?
Singha.
There’s this ancient book from a long time ago.
It was crafted entirely from human skin.
The one who possesses this book.
By using the blood from
the four elements to read this book.
The book can be opened.
Inside, you'll find the secret spells.
Anyone who reads it.
Will have a spirit stronger than anyone alive.
And become invulnerable.
I think.
I’ll be seeing that book very soon.
Hey, what the hell? I’m trying to sleep here!
Find this person for me.
The photo's blurry, but I'll check.
Business been slow lately?
Yes, Mr. God.
It’s been like this for two or three months now.
That amulet I got from you
worked for over a year, but now nothing.
The magic must have faded.
Gosh!
You’ve murdered my man
The Liquor Spell.
Ohm... Tuk- Tuk... Tak- Tak...
Stone and cliffs are broken within my head.
My head is an iron helmet.
My body is like
diamond- steel, spears, and swords.
My body is as resilient as bamboo.
Harpoons, spikes, and javelins.
Spears and swords.
Crossbows and muskets.
My teacher is named Maha Thameun.
Like the earth that is unshaken and unafraid.
(Chanting)
Flesh to flesh.
Bone to bone.
เลือดต่อเลือด
Sinew to sinew.
Ohm, rejoice, let them become one body.
By will, it is manifested.
By will, it is dissolved.
Make the mind stronger than all others.
Use these mystic arts only with wisdom and grace.
It all depends on your choice.
Hey, you.
You.
What are you going to do? Hey.
Hey.
Hey, you.
You.
What the fuck?
Singha.
Once you have focus.
You will see things that others don't see.
Luang Phor also performed
that eyeopening ritual for you.
Those who have dead.
They are bound to haunt
the same places repeatedly.
It’s their karma.
Whatever they remembered
right before they died.
they’ll just keep doing that on a loop.
Unlike spirits holding a grudge.
They will not find peace or seek rebirth.
They’re only obsessed with getting revenge.
So, Why is it that
I am the one who has to see them?
One day, you’ll understand it on your own.
But if you really want to know.
Just close your eyes and try to meditate.
What do you see in the darkness?
Keep your mind centered.
Right there between life and death.
There’s something else.
It’s here.
Its body...
Its body is black.
Singha.
It’s calling my name.
Singha! Come out! Singha.
Singha.
Singha! Come out.
Hey Chai, let’s have a drink.
I brought some booze for you.
Drink up, buddy!
Hey! What are you doing?
Why?
I give to my friend.
He died.
He likes to drink.
whoa, hold on. Are you taking a photo?
No. No.
Okay, take it.
Looking sharp.
Awesome.
Thank you.
Next time, bring the photo
to show me.I'll give you a 10% discount.
The owner.
Shit.
What the hell?
Are you alright, Lieutenant?
It’s nothing.
Inspector, do you believe in.
the occult, or things like ghosts and demons?
I didn't use to.
But now, I do.
Have you actually seen the real thing before?
Even if I have, I wouldn't go so
far as to confirm they truly exist.
When it happened.
our mind might have just made it up.
If we explain it scientifically.
It could be from lack of sleep.
Low spirits, or just hallucinations.
Wait.
Then what about you saying you believe?
The reason I believe.
Is to confirm that some things
that happened are actually real.
That there is real evil and real good.
Occultism itself has both black and white sides.
If the dark arts emerge.
We must find the light to subdue it.
If we don't believe in anything at all.
We’ll have no anchor to hold onto.
We must have faith.
We must have belief.
Because it gives us something to stand for.
And allows us to see the other side.
The information identifies him as Cambodian.
His name is Mr. Bong Pa- on,
and he works as an undertaker.
So, why did he come to Thailand?
Inspector.
I think it’s this way.
Lieutenant.
This one. It looks exactly like this.
- I see. Let’s go check it out.
- Yes.
Watch the car.
It’s very dark.
- Sarge, give us some light.
- Got it.
Lieutenant.
There's a room inside.
All clear.
There’s another room.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Lieutenant.
Toon isn't picking up her phone.
I’m stuck with all this mess again.
And they both disappeared at the same time.
Oh shit, look at this.
How about this?
Wait, wait. Today, the two of us.
We're not doing a damn thing.
Let’s just call it a day.
It'll be chill. Let’s go find something else to do.
You’re unbelievable. You are so lazy.
- You in?
- Heh.
If anyone asks.
I’m telling them it was your idea.
You bitched so much I thought you weren't in.
Ok, Let’s call it a day.
- So, you in? Let’s get some food.
- I want some spicy salad.
- Alright, alright. Let's go.
- Singha's here! He's here!
- Wow, such a hard worker!
- Oh my god, there’s so much dust!
- So much dust, ugh.
- Here, wipe yourself too. You’re filthy.
The dust is on the floor.
Oh, look at Mr. Stylish.
Is it snowing at your house? Aren't you sweating?
- Sure, it’s hot.
- Snow.
Whoa.
Johnny Depp.
Hey.
Did your tattoos get clearer?
I don’t think they’re just clearer.
Looking like this? It's obvious.
Whoa, not an inch of skin left.
Are you addicted to the needle or what?
Let's just open a shop already.
Fucking cool. You’re cool.
You, go work!
You tired from working, you bastard?
Come here, let me wipe your face.
Nice. So much sweat. Hey!
You bastard!
A table rag on my face? I’ll hit you with a broom!
Don't.
No.
- So, what’s wrong with her anyway?
- Don't.
No.
Hold on.
Did you get those tattoos at the same place?
Yeah.
One more week of this
sleeping act and I’m calling the police.
I’ve been wiping her down so much,
I could practically be a nurse by now.
Hey.
Hey, guys.
Foot's twitching!
My feet.
Not your foot. It’s her foot that’s twitching.
What's with you, Joe?
- Gosh!
- Don’t tell me you two didn’t see that.
See what?
What the hell is wrong with you?
I’m serious, I really saw it. Her foot twitched!
Gosh.
Shit.
Shit, I forgot to buy meat.
Come on, come with me.
Go where? No way.
I want to see the foot twitch again.
- Ow! Are you coming or not?
- Agh!
- Alright, alright! I'm going.
- Stop whining. Hurry up.
Who actually are you?
- Hey.
- Hey, you.
What are you doing?
Calm down and stop.
Stop.
Please, stay calm.
Stop right there.
Stop it.
Focus! Just stay calm.
Nam... Tip.
Where am I?
This is Pattaya.
I rescued you from the sea.
It looked like you were running from something.
I'm Singha.
What's your name?
I can't remember.
Shit, what the hell is this?
(Khmer chanting)
I call upon the spirits.
That dwell within this land.
Drive these nails into them.
This isn't what we agreed upon.
You said you'd pick me up,
but you never showed.
Pay the remaining fee.
After this job is done,
the price has changed.
The rate is going up.
Their magic is too strong. It was a hard job.
Don't screw me over. That's it.
Go back to where you came from.
The man in the photo is Bong Pa- on.
A Cambodian and an undertaker by profession.
In other words,
the villagers call him a shaman.
He specializes in dark amulets.
Incantations, and sorcery.
That symbol is the Soul - Binding Needle.
According to local belief.
Since he moved to Pattaya.
The death toll has been steadily rising.
It means Bong Pa - on is
linked to every case.
where every victim's
forehead was carved with Khmer script.
So, what's his motive for the killings?
Perhaps it’s all just a diversion.
Or maybe...
Believe it or not.
But in the realm of the occult.
a violent, unnatural death is a
way to enhance one's spiritual power.
So that he can harvest those
souls to feed the spirits he commands.
So, based on your analysis.
It means the victims
weren't the killer's actual targets.
I’m not afraid of you.
What are you doing this for, huh?
To take your soul.
You.
You really are no match for me.
How about it?
Want to be my house - bound spirit?
Coming?
Who sent you?
Alright! I'll tell you!
I’m telling!
Arnon.